Banks McLaurin, Jr. stereograph collection
DeGolyer Library
- Boxed Travel Sets, Series 16:
  - Box Sets (Box 19)
    - Tour of the World, Vol. I, Vol. II, Stereographic Library. Boxed set of 102.
      - 328 W33233 Berchtergarden
      - 336 W33236 Heidelberg on the Neckar
      - 326 W24581 Upper Hall in the Hof Brauhaus, Munich
      - 341 30061 Rheinstein Castle on the Rhine
      - 340 30058 T/W24502 Ehrenfels Castle on the Rhine
      - 313 30063 Potsdammer Platz, Berlin
      - Great Britain - England
      - 213 V28269 St. Michael's Mount, Cornwall
      - 238 33017 Heart of London
      - 209 3087 T/3064 Tower of Magdalene College, Oxford
      - 247 28303 Old Roman Walls from York Minister, York
      - 243 3064 T Windsor Castle from the Thames
      - 221 13160 Quaint cottages, Isle of Wight
      - 205 8089/355(3012) Anne Hathway's Cottage, Shottery
      - 203 V25461 Hunting hounds, Shropshire
      - 210 V25477 Lynmouth, English Alps
      - 235 3084T/3061 Old Curiosity Shop, London
      - 241 13101T Overlooking the Thames at night, London
      - Ireland
      - 177 V12687 T Ross Castle, Lakes of Killarney
      - 176 V12639 T Lower Lake, Killarney
      - Scotland
      - 195 2649T Sterling Castle
      - 191 2659T Loch Katrine
      - 192 12703 T A Highland House
      - 194 2657 T Overlooking the Tay
      - 199 V12736 T Princes Street, Edinburgh
      - 198 2672 Abbotsford, residence of Sir Walter Scott
      - Guatemala
      - T240 12872 (291) Esquintas, Twin Volcanoes
      - Iceland
      - 254 33167 A summer stroll, Reykjavik
      - Luxemborg
      - 400 V33274 Luxemborg
      - Mexico
      - 53 24157 Governor's Palace, Monterey
      - 52 V23653 Monterey, Mexico's largest manufacturing city
      - 67 23761 Waterfront of Mazatlan
      - 82 23783/23693 At the bull fight, Mexico City
      - 70 23769 Falls of Juanacatlem, Jalisco
      - 92 16185 Taxco Church
      - 88 23657 T Ixtacihuatl
      - 84 24160 Xochimilco
      - 78 23775 National Palace, Mexico City
      - 65 23758 Cathedral in Culiacan
      - Monaco
      - 442 33305 Monte Carlo on the Riviera
      - Netherlands
      - 363 25245 Peace Palace, The Hague
      - 353 12213 The Amstel, Amsterdam
      - 352 V12218 Amsterdam from Zuider Kirk
      - 366 25680 River parallel canal, Rotterdam
      - Norway
      - 281 25626 Little Stave Church at Byglo, Oslo
      - 277 33170 Oslo on a summer night
      - 266 V15794 Placid Lake Oldenay and Grytereids Glacier
      - 260 25629 Hillside farm near Engan
      - 270 V25640 Charming Odde
      - 251 25646 Bergen from Floifjeld
      - Palestine
      - 33280 Church of the Nativity, Bethlehem
      - 3117 Church of the Nativity, Bethlehem
      - Peru
      - T48 V21910 T Heart of the Andes
      - 125 21939 Aeroquioshe and Elmisto
      - United States
      - T5 26490 T Washington Monument, Wash., DC
      - T3 32229 The Dazzling dome of the Capital, Wash., DC
      - T6 32185 The White House, Wash., DC
      - T2 26100 T Wash., DC from an airplane
      - H25 26337 Plymouth Rock, Plymouth, MA
      - T37 32823 T Manhattan from the air (Fairchild Aerial Surveys)
      - T34 26293 T New York City from an airplane
      - T16 34412 Pittsburgh, PA at night, from Mt. Washington
      - T14 32731 The Civic Center at Pittsburgh from the air
      - H37 26319 William Penn's house, Fairmount Park, Philadelphia
      - T13 V23221 T Horseshoe Curve, Allegheny Mts., PA
      - T12 32568 T Devil's Den, scene of fierce fighting, Gettysburg, PA
      - 1 White Coral without third dimension effect
      - 2 4306 White Coral with third dimension effect
      - Panama
      - 114 20877 City and bay of Panama from Ancontril
      - Puerto Rico
      - 159 V10287 Rural Puerto Rico
      - Sweden
      - 300 25250 Helsingborg
      - Venezuela
      - 147 V21890 T Overlooking Caracas
    - Tour of the World. Keystone View Co. Set of 199 stereos ca. 1895-1909 in an oak box with two stereo viewers patented 1904; probable date of issue is 1909. Stereos are numbered on back (stamped) 1-200 with 71 missing.
      - 116 Bridge of Sighs, Venice, Italy
      - 171 American Falls, Niagara, NY, USA, ca. 1901
      - 224 Capitol, Washington, DC, USA, ca. 1900
      - 246 Coconut Grove, Lake Worth, FL, USA, ca. 1897
      - 387 Natural Bridge, VA, USA, ca. 1897
      - 1007 In the surf, Atlantic City, NJ, USA
      - 1603 The Grand Opera, Paris, France
      - 1619 Arch of Triumph, Garden of the Tuileries, Paris, France, ca. 1896
      - 1641 Avenue des Champs Elysees, Paris, France, ca. 1900
      - 1721 Court of the Lions, Alhambra, Granada, Spain, ca. 1896
      - 1871 Axenstrasse Tunnel, Lake Lucerne, Switzerland, ca. 1901
      - 1901 Rome, the Eternal City, from St. Peter's, Rome, Italy, ca. 1904
      - 1907 The Roman Forum, Rome, Italy, ca. 1904
      - 1958 The Leaning Tower of Pisa, Italy, ca. 1895
      - 2471 The Bowery, New York City, NY, USA, ca. 1897
      - 2500 Lakes of Killarney, Ireland, ca. 1902
      - 2503 Blarney Castle, Ireland, ca. 1897
      - 2047 Market Place, Cologne, Germany, ca. 1896
      - 2111 Tower of London, England, ca. 1901
      - 2601 Princess St. and Waverly Gardens, Edinburgh, Scotland, ca. 1902
      - 2626 The Valley of Tay, Scotland, ca. 1898
      - 2713 The Artist's Dream, bettws-y-Coed, North Wales, ca. 1897
      - 3002 Westminster Abbey, London, England, ca. 1900
      - 3012 Anne Hathaway's Cottage, Shottery, England, ca. 1897
      - 5004 Glacier Point, Yosemite, Valley, CA, USA, ca. 1899
      - 5007 The Fallen Monarch, Mariposa Grove, Yosemite Valley, CA, USA, ca. 1897
      - 5041 Characteristics Holland
      - 5048 Cliff House and Seal Rocks, San Francisco, CA, USA, ca. 1901
      - 5075 Birdseye View of Union Stockyards, Chicago, IL, USA, ca. 1897
      - 6044 Mormon Temple and Tabernacle, Salt Lake City, UT, ca. 1897
      - 6465 The Duomo or Cathedral, Florence, Italy, ca. 1905
      - 6983 Independence Hall, Philadelphia, PA, USA, ca. 1905 by B.L. Singley
      - 7170 Treading out the grain, threshing as in the olden days, Greece ca. 1906 by Keystone View Co.
      - 7304 View of Jerusalem from Mount of Olives, Palestine, ca. 1906
      - 8002 Royal George, Grand Canyon of the Arkansas, CO, USA, ca. 1897
      - 8008 in the Heart of Box Canyon (near Ouray) CO, USA, ca. 1901
      - 8014 Cliff palace in the Mesa Verde, CO, USA, ca. 1898
      - 8016 Dining room, Soldier's Home, Marion, IN, USA, ca. 1901
      - 8046 Congressional Library, Washington, D.C., USA, ca. 1900
      - 9195 Preparing to climb the golden stair, Chilkoot Pass, Alaska, ca. 1898
      - 9434 Washington St., showing Old South Meetinghouse, Boston, MA, ca. 1898
      - 9451 Glory Enough for One Day (shot in Aroostock Co., ME), ca. 1899
      - 9460 Laliberte's Fur Parlor, Quebec, Canada, ca. 1899
      - 9466 Beautiful Mirror Lake, Yosemite Valley, CA, USA, ca. 1899
      - 9506 "We's done all dis s'morning," ca. 1899 by BLS ca. 1905 by KV Co.
      - 9676 Leaping to Stand Rock, Wisconsin Dells, WI, USA, ca. 1899
      - 9737 Ruins of Karnak, Egypt, ca. 1899
      - 9759 Threshing Beans in the Field, Egypt, ca. 1899 by BLS, ca. 1910 by KV Co.
      - 9774 Tilling the Soil as in Ancient Days, Egypt, ca. 1899
      - 9779 With the flocks, Egypt, ca. 1899
      - 9781 The Sphinx, Gizah, Egypt, c. 1899
      - 9786 Bird’s Eye View of Cairo, Egypt, c. 1899
      - 9788 Mosque of Mohammed Ali, Cairo, Egypt, c. 1899
      - 9812 Inundation of the Nile, Egypt, c. 1900
      - 10053 Mayon, the peerless cone of Southern Luzon, n. Legaspi, PI, c. 1906
      - 10064 Filipino farmers harrowing rice fields, n. Manila, PI, c. 1906
      - 10068 Threshing rice with carabao, Luzon, PI, c. 1906
      - 10070 Hulling Rice for Breakfast, Luzon, PI, c. 1906
      - 10074 Husking cocoanuts, n. Pagsanjan, Luzon, PI, c. 1906
      - 10103 Dog Team, Antwerp, Belgium, c. 1900
      - 10151 Government House, formerly the Palace, Honolulu, Hawaii, c. 1901
      - 10265 Taking time on a Sugar Plantation, Porto Rico, c. 1900
      - 10304 Throne Room, Royal Palace, Berlin, Germany, c. 1900
      - 10325 A street scene in Hamburg, Germany, c. 1901
      - 10346 The Rhine from Drachenfels, Germany, c. 1903
      - 10348 Castle Rheinstein from Gunner’s Watch, Germany, c. 1900
      - 10352 Toiling in the Vineyards, Rudesheim, Germany, c. 1904
      - 10558 The Great Brooklyn Bridge, New York City, NY, USA, c. 1900
      - 10637 Parliament Bldg, Toronto, Canada, c. 1901
      - 10692 The buffalo in his snow-bound home, BC, Canada, c. 1903
      - 10706 The Wetterhorn form Grindelwald, Switzerland, c. 1900
      - 10708 Guide cutting steps, Upper Glacier, Grindelwald, Switzerland, c. 1900
      - 10745 Entrance to the Gorge of the Aras, Meiringen, Switzerland, c. 1900
      - 10750 Lauterbrunnen Valley and Staubbach Fall, Switzerland, c. 1901
      - 10765 Looking at the Matterhorn form Riffelburg Hotel, Switzerland, c. 1901
      - 10768 Mountain Corridors, Gorner Gorge, Switzerland, c. 1901
      - 10804 City of Mexico, Ancient Tenochtitlan of the Aztecs, c. 1900
      - 10843 Public Fountain, San Luis Potosi, Mexico, c. 1900
      - 10896 Art creation by the Master Hand, Acambaro, Mexico, c. 1900
      - 10931 Scene of the Passion play, Ober-Ammergao, Germany, c. 1901
      - 10953 The Famous Galata Bridge, Constantinople, Turkey, c. 1900
      - 11002 Garden of Gethsemane and Mt. of Olives, Palestine, c. 1900
      - 11004 Jews’ Wailing Place, Jerusalem, Palestine, c. 1899
      - 11054 Jaffa from the sea, Palestine, c. 1900
      - 11059 A coffee house in Palestine, c. 1900
      - 11068 Jordan and the Promised Land, Palestine, c. 1900
      - 11070 Nazareth, Palestine, c. 1900
      - 11132 Cedars of Lebanon, Syria, c. 1900
      - 11161 The Acropolis from Philoppapos Hill, Athens, Greece, c. 1900
      - 11186 Jerusalem, a City of Domes, Palestine, c. 1906
      - 11200 The Tiber, Castle of San Angelo and St. Peter’s, Rome, Italy, c.1904
      - 11205 The Library of the Vatican, Rome, Italy, c. 1900
      - 11206 Hall of the Immaculate Conception, the Vatican, Rome, Italy, c. 1900
      - 11225 Pope Leo lying in State, Rome, Italy, c. 1903
      - 11234 Coliseum, the King of Ruins, Rome, Italy, c. 1903
      - 11235 Overlooking the Vatican and Tiber from St. Peter’s Rome, Italy, c. 1903
      - 11244 Piazza di San Marco, Venice, Italy, c. 1903
      - 11248 The majestic Duomo, Milan, Italy, c. 1904
      - 11305 Looking towards the Strand from Trafalgar Square, London, Eng., c. 1901
      - 11475 Roundup on the Sherman Ranch, Genesee, KS, USA, c. 1902
      - 11623 Harvesting in the Great West, Washington, USA, ca. 1901
      - 11625 Shooting Prairie Chickens, ca. 1901
      - 11661 Nature's Wondrous Gorge Spanned by Man's Ingenuity, Georgetown, CO, USA, ca. 1901
      - 11680 Lexington common, MA, USA, ca. 1901
      - 11766 Women washing clothes, Nice, France, ca. 1900
      - 11751 The Casino, Monte Carlo, Monaco, ca. 1900
      - 11798 Promenade des Planches, Trouville-sur Mer, Normandy, France, ca. 1909
      - 11885 Jinrikisha and Banyan Tree, Durban, Natal, South Africa, ca. 1901
      - 11896 Government Ave, Cape Town, South Africa, ca. 1901
      - 11917 Still There's No Place Like Home, ca. 1901
      - 12006 Interior of Throne Room, Forbidden City, Peking, China, ca. 1900
      - 12014 A Chinese Saw Mill, Peking, China, ca. 1900
      - 12050 The Renowned prospect from the Peak, Hong Kong, China, ca. 1900
      - 12101 Colombo Harbor from Landing Jetty, Ceylon, ca. 1901
      - 12269 Wild Elk, Montana, USA, ca. 1904
      - 12456 Hudson River Valley, NY, USA, ca. 1902
      - 12509 Mahratta Durbar Hall, Rajah's Palace, Tonjore, India, ca. 1901
      - 12515 Interior, Dilwara Temple, Mount Abu, India, ca. 1901
      - 12526 A Characteristic Street in Mandura, India, ca. 1902
      - 12521 The Taj Mahal, Agra, India, ca. 1902
      - 12600 Suspension Bridge, Kenmare, Ireland, ca. 1902
      - 12615 A Letter from Pat in America, Ireland, ca. 1902
      - 12702 A Highland Home, Scotland, ca. 1902
      - 12703 Historic Sterling Castle, Scotland, ca. 1902
      - 12707 Traveling through the Trosachs, Scotland, ca. 1902
      - 12804 Harvesting Bananas, Costa Rica, CA.A., ca. 1902
      - 12860 Tortilla Making, Salvador, CA.A., ca. 1902
      - 13408 In the Fair and Fertile Jordal Valley, Norway, ca. 1903
      - 13409 Taking Hay Down from the Mountains, Norway, ca. 1903
      - 13422 Milking the Goats, Hardanger Fjord, Norway, ca. 1903
      - 13424 Norwegian wedding Party, Hardanger, Norway, ca. 1903
      - 13315 In the narrow streets of La Guayra, Venezuela, ca. 1902
      - 13393 Where the Lotefos and Skarsfos Meet, Hardanger, Norway, ca. 1906
      - 13101 Overlooking the Thames at night, London, England, ca. 1902
      - 13120 Lake Grasmere and Village from Red Bank, Lake Dist., England, ca. 1904
      - 13003 Council Room, Royal Palace, Stockholm, Sweden, ca. 1901
      - 13019 Path cut in Granite, mountainside near Trolhatta, Sweden, ca. 1906
      - 13077 The Round Tower, Copenhagen, Denmark, ca. 1901
      - 13080 Queen Louise Bridge, Copenhagen, Denmark, ca. 1901
      - 13504 Flat Iron Bldg., Fifth Ave. Broadway, NY City, NY, USA, ca. 1903
      - 13512 Balanced Rock, Garden of the Gods, CO, USA, ca. 1903
      - 13520 Grand Canyon, AZ, USA, ca. 1903
      - 13532 Los Angeles Pigeon Farm, CA, USA, ca. 1903
      - 13528 Cawston Ostrich Farm, CA, USA
      - 13538 Ten Acres of Calla Lilies, southern, CA, USA, ca. 1903
      - 13546 More than 10,000 acres of Orange Groves, San Gabriel Valley, CA., ca. 1903
      - 13567 One of the great trees in the rain forest of OR, USA, ca. 1903
      - 13577 Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone National Park, WY, USA, ca. 1904
      - 13579 Gap of the Golden Gate Winter, Yellowstone National Park, WY, ca. 1904
      - 13584 Old Faithful, Queen of Geysers, Yellowstone, WY, USA, ca. 1904
      - 13588 Angel Terrace, Yellowstone, WY, USA, c. 1904
      - 13595 The Noisy Roadside Growler, Yellowstone, WY, USA, c. 1904
      - 13596 The Famous Fish Pot, Yellowstone, WY, USA, c.1904
      - 13602 Interior of Congressional Library, Wash, DC, c. 1903
      - 13619 Ship Mast being shipped from Port Blakely Mills, Largest Lumber Mills in USA, n. Seattle, WA
      - 13624 First Haul of the Season, Salmon Industry, Columbia River, OR, USA, c. 1904
      - 13637 Mt. Hood, near its crest, OR, USA, c. 1904
      - 13647 The Shepherd and his flock, MT, USA, c. 1904
      - 13701 Marble Quarry, Proctor, VT, USA, c. 1903
      - 13740 Harvesting Indian River Pineapples, FL, USA, c. 1904
      - 13741 Cultivating Rice, SC, USA, c. 1904
      - 13747 A Turpentine Farm, Savannah, GA, USA, c.1904
      - 13772 Up Broadway and Fifth Ave., NY City, NY, USA, c.1904
      - 13790 Sixty Five Acres of Hops, OR, USA, c.1905
      - 13802 Among the Wonderful Ice Peaks, Illecillewaet Glacier, BC, Can., c. 1903
      - 13806 Mt. Sir Donald, Matterhorn of NA Alps, BC, Canada, c.1903
      - 13809 Lake Louise and Glaciers of Mt. Victoria, from Chalet, Alberta, Canada, c. 1903
      - 13822 Moraine Lake, Canadian Lakes, BC, Canada, c. 1903
      - 13885 A Shady Nook, Montmorency River, Quebec, Canada, c. 1903
      - 13886 Quiatchouan Falls, n. St. John, NB, Canada, c. 1903
      - 13895 In the Arcadian land, Nova Scotia, Canada, c. 1903
      - 13987 View from Dufferin Terrace, Quebec, Canada, c. 1906
      - 13993 Street of French Canadian Village, c. 1906
      - 14004 Japanese Girls in Suisenji park, Kumamoto, Japan, c. 1901
      - 14047 An Idyllic Spot for Jap. Maids to Stroll, Japan, c. 1904
      - 14076 White Robed Potter Peddlers, Seole, Korea, c. 1901
      - 14081 Plowing Scene near Seole, Korea, c. 1901
      - 14244 Water front of NY City from Brooklyn, c. 1908
      - 14327 Path of the Red-Hot Hurricane, St. Pierre, Martinique, FWI, c. 1902
      - 14355 Volcanic Eruption, Gros Morne, Martinique, FWI, c. 1903
      - 14416 Soufriere’s Mammouth Crater, St. Vincent, FWI, c. 1902
      - 14437 Mighty Earthquake Fissures, Guadaloupe, FWI, c. 1903
      - 14710 Tea and Rice near Shizuoka, Japan, c. 1904
      - 14757 Japan’s largest Silk Weaving Plants, Am Methods, Kiryu, Japan, c. 1904
      - 14730 Rice Planters at Work, Japan, c. 1904
      - 14812 Fuji-San, Japan, c. 1905
      - 15808 Harbor of Barcelona, Spain, c. 1906
      - 15827 A Peasant at Home, Valencia, Spain, c. 1906
      - 15901 Melbourne, Australia from Dome of Exhibition Bldg., c. 1908
      - 15913 Typical Natives of the Fiji Island, Suva, c. 1908
      - 15914 Native Grass House, Suva, Fiji Islands, c. 1908
      - 16507 San Francisco Bay during visit of Pacific Fleet, CA, c. 1908
      - 20197 A Mountain of Oysters Ready for Shipping, Hampton, VA, c. 1907
      - 20877 Looking down on the City of Panama, Canal Zone, c. 1906
      - 20860 Tropical Vegetation, Panama Canal, c. 1906
      - 20861 Culebra Cut, Looking North, Panama Canal, CZ, c. 1906
      - 20862 The indispensable American Steam Shovel, Panama Canal, CZ, c. 1906
      - 20881 Spanish Laborers at Work on the Panama Canal, CZ, c. 1909
    - World War Through the Stereoscope, Keystone View Co. Set of 48 in box – none missing. Bought in Marshall, TX, Dec. 1990.
      - 1 15625 Sarajevo, Yugoslavia
      - 2 10331 Parade, Berlin, Germany
      - 3 18689 Russian Troops on review
      - 4 V-18825 Tangled Ruins of Marne Bridge
      - 5 V-18858 German Dead in La Basse Area
      - 6 V-18840 No Mans Land near Lens, France
      - 7 V-18874 Proud Men of the North who fought at Flanders Field
      - 8 V-18865 Battle of Cambria
      - 9 V-18862 Scots Entrenched
      - 10 V-18826 Pres. Poincore and Marshall Joffre at Somme Front
      - 11 18765 Cathedral of Reims, France in ruins
      - 12 18834 Desolate Waste at Chemin des Dames Sector
      - 13 18835 Camouflaged Trench, Chemin des Dames Sector
      - 14 18633 French Soldiers Resting
      - 15 18817 The Horrors of War
      - 16 V-18911 Feeding
      - 17 18651 French 155 MM Gun
      - 18 18832 French Troops Inspecting Wrecked Zeppelin
      - 19 18927 Enemy Airmen bombed one of our supply trains
      - 20 19191 U.S. Observation Airplane
      - 21 18756 French 75 in action
      - 22 V-19216 Dirigible R-34 at Mineola
      - 23 V-18898 Shells Bursting in French Village
      - 24 19149 Hugh Armored Tank
      - 25 19000 Pres. Wilson Addressing Congress
      - 26 19198 Learning to use gas mask
      - 27 18360 Building Barbed Wire Entanglement, Ft. Sheldon, IL
      - 28 19100 Our answer to the Kaiser
      - 29 19192 Thousands Marching – our National Army
      - 30 19193 Thousands of Uncle Sam's Sailors
      - 31 19004 Four of our Subs in dry dock in Navy Yard
      - 32 V-188948 Joffre Pershing in Paris
      - 33 18715 View of Famous Bridge over the Marne
      - 34 V-18948 In Belleau Wood where Americans checked Germany
      - 35 V-199249 Grave of Lt. Quentin Roosevelt
      - 36 19248 The Place des Halles, St. Mihiel
      - 37 19249 The Stars Stripes flying over Ehrenbreltstein, Germany
      - 38 V-19229 Doughboys of 89th Div., Treves, Germany
      - 39 V-19230 Gen. Pershing decorating officers of 89th
      - 40 19209 Uncle Sam John Bull parading in London
      - 41 18775 Victory day celebration, 14 Jul 1919, Paris
      - 42 18781 Clemenceau, Wilson Lloyd George Washington
      - 43 V-19237 U.S. Transport Leviathan formerly Vaterland
      - 44 V-19266 Some of our 2 million troops, Brest, France
      - 45 V-19217 Abandon Ship Drill by U.S. Troops
      - 46 19153 Happy reunion
      - 47 23306 Back to Homeland by Unknown Solider
      - 48 13365 America's Most Notable gathering of Military Heroes
    - Yosemite Valley, Stereoscopic Library. Keystone View Co. Underwood Underwood set on Yosemite National Park dated 1902. Including map and book, Yosemite Valley Through the Stereoscope, copyright, 1902, 1908.
      - 1. 6017 UU S288 (ENE) From Inspiration Point, showing Bridal Vail Falls
      - 2. 6018 c. UU El Capitan east to Half Dome
      - 3. 6019 c. UU Ribbon Falls looking N from Valley
      - 4. 6020 c. UU El Capitan, a granite mountain 3300' tall
      - 5. 6021 c. UU The Three Brothers
      - 6. 6022 c. UU North Dome, Half Dome and Cloud's Rest
      - 7. 6023 c. UU Mirror View of Cathedral Rocks
      - 8. 6024 c. UU Amidst Yosemite's charms – Sentinel Hotel
      - 9. 6025 c. UU Majestic Yosemite Point Yosemite Falls
      - 10. 6026 c. UU The Valley, Half Dome, Nevada Falls
      - 11. 6027 c. UU Yosemite Falls from Glacier Point trail
      - 12. 6028 c. UU Looking up the sheer face of Glacier Point
      - 13. 6029 c. UU Looking down from Overhanging Rocks
      - 14. 6030 c. UU Nearly a mile down and only a step from Glacier Point
      - 15. 6031 c. UU Overlooking scenery from Glacier Point
      - 16. 6032 c. UU From Glacier Point, over Mirror Lake, Half Dome
      - 17. 6033 c. UU Nevada and Vernal Falls from Glacier Point
      - 18. 6034 c. UU Amid majestic heights and chasm of Yosemite Valley
      - 19. 6035 c. UU On the brink of a fearful chasm from Glacier Canyon
      - 20. 6036 c. UU Climbing up a steep zigzag trail at Eastern end of Valley
      - 21. 6037 c. UU Nevada Falls and Cap of Liberty
      - 22. 6038 c. UU Mirror Lake looking NW
      - 23. 6039 c. UU From Clouds Rest over Lake Tenaiya
      - 24. 6040 c. UU From Clouds Rest SE towards Mt. Clark
- Stereoscopes, True-Vue and View-Master Viewers, and Magic Lantern Projectors, Series 17:
  - A set of two "Monarch" stereoscopes, manufactured by Keystone View Co., Meadville, PA, patented Apr. 12, 1904 in tiger oak wooden box with set of 200 Tour of the World stereos, published ca. 1909. Bought Oct. 24, 1991 from estate of Mrs. Alvin H. Lane. $550 (Box 20)
  - Viewer: Alexander Beckers burl walnut wood viewer. 50 stereos can be mounted in it, and there is a handle to rotate them. Has a flip up mirror to facilitate viewing regular views and tissues, dates ca. 1860. Bought Feb. 3, 1992 from Lower Greenville Antique Mall. $460
  - Viewer: Federal, 40-T01 all metal viewer on an adjustable stand for use in schools and libraries. Bought in Jefferson, TX in ca. 1987 for $125, which included about 15-20 views.
  - 1. Claudet-style wooden viewer veneered, flip up mirror for viewing stereos, can view tissues through lens. C.F. Clifford, 30 Piccadilly, London, England. Will accommodate 3 9/32 x 6 5/8 tissue or stereos (vs. normal 3 ½ x 7) indicating it was manufactured ca. 1855/60. Bought at McKinney Ave. Antique Mall; Xmas present from Louise 1992 $379.75 (Box 21)
  - 2. Stereographoscope probably manufactured in France ca. 1890, purchased at Unlimited, Ltd. on May 11, 1994 along with stereos made by Rotary Photographic Co. of London for $220 tax included.
  - 3. Verascope Richard. Stereoscope, Brevete S.G.D.G. Vues Prises Avec Le Verascope Richard, ca. 1893. Bought at Unlimited, Ltd. on May 17, 1994 along with 17 thin glass views made by Wellington, 1 ¾ x 4 ¼".
  - 4. The "Paragon" Scope, Keystone View Co. Patented USA, Oct. 15, 1896; USA, Jan. 18, 1898; Canada Feb. 1, 1896; Germany, France, Great Britain, Australia, Belgium. Birdseye maple wood with red velvet around eye piece with brass fittings and hardware. Bought at Memories Mall, Richardson, TX Aug. 13, 1994 for $165 including 39 stereos 1896-1901 period – all the old mountings of Keystone rather than gray.
  - 5. The "Perfecscope," trade mark, patent Oct. 15, 1895, H.C. White Co. Embossed on top of hood, "Exposition Universelle Internationale, 1900" [Paris].
  - 6. Underwood Underwood "Sun Sculpture" trademark stereoscope patented June 11, 1901. (Box 22)